If you are thinking of buying the electric scooter that they have launched in the market, then it must be
coming to your mind that
how will its insurance be done, this video is
for you, in this we will give information about
which insurance
is mandatory with the scooter and what is optional, so the
mandatory insurance that the company has kept is
one year and damage and five year third party
insurance, this means that your vehicle will be valid for
one year in this and if your vehicle
hits someone else's tractor, then
your liability in that will be
covered in a special policy for five years, apart from this best
policy, you can also take an advance in it, the
advance is personal accident cover of emergency
situation and roadside assistance, these
are all options as I said, but the
mandatory one year and damage in five year
third party insurance policy,
you can also buy this insurance policy from the company's website
or electric app and the
insurance partner of the company
is ICICI Lombard,
we will bring more updates on this subject in our next video, stay tuned to
our channel, thank you